Easy.
>> Why are you down? Hey,
>> why are you downloading?
Hey, why you downloading? One minute in.
You don't like this? Are you Jewish?
Does it bother you that the new that
reality is happening? Does it bother
you? Why are you downloading this?
Are you a Jew?
The guy is talking about how
you know the real world is happening. If
you don't like it, you you you're free
to close your eyes and leave the stream
right away.
Right? If you don't like the news, if
you if you instantly come here and you
don't like it, you are absolutely free
to go and do anything else with your
life. But maybe you're a person that's
just like, I don't like anything. I
don't like anything. I don't like this
video. I don't like that. Like maybe
you're just a person like that. Maybe
that's just your life. Maybe you're just
like a person that don't like anything.
But if you come in here one minute past
and you don't like the video because
he's talking about how Jews
of the world are doing horrible things
in Europe and in Israel and other
places. And that's a travesty, a human
degradation if you will. and the things
that are happening as a result of that
in Europe and other places. You don't
like that? I don't like that either. You
don't got to download my video for it. I
don't like I don't like the world
either. Can you guess what? I don't like
these people, right? I don't like the
things that are happening in Europe. I
don't like the things that are happening
in America. I don't like the world at
all. So, we agree, but you don't got to
download me. I'm just a messenger. Like,
why do you do that? Like, I'm just the
messenger. I'm just here to to let you
know that the world is burning, but you
don't got to hate. I'm just a messenger,
dude. Like, what? What the [__] did I do
to you? You hired 10 seconds, you
download the video instantly. What
What's wrong with you? At least give it
some time so you can have an opinion.
So, so you can form an opinion.
It's It's just dumb. Like, you download
what? It's headless. It's brainless. Why
do you do that? Why?
I know it's because you have low IQ or
you have no brain or something like
this, but why? Like why? Why? Actually,
why? Like, have you like I know this is
going to be hard for you, but have you
ever just stopped
and started reflecting on what you're
doing with your life, what you're doing
with your time, what you're doing here,
what you're doing in general? If you
hate me so much, you want to download me
instantly every single day of your life.
You are sad and pathetic and you should
reconsider what you're doing with your
life, then I would urge you to think
about that.
But you don't want to think, do you? You
just want to be mad. You just want to be
rotten at the core, right? You just want
to show that
you're like rotten person. For every
moment in your life, you just spend it
being rotten.
That's why there's cancer growing inside
of you. And that's why I'll never get
cancer. And that's why I'm better than
you in every single way. Because you
don't know what's good for you. You
waste your time doing things that are no
good for you. Your brain is full of rot.
And so instead of emptying that, doing
anything else, you give rise to
cancerous growth. You give rise to
death. You give rise to rot. You give
rise to all kinds of things. If you fill
up this brain with [__] you're not
going to have space to think. That's
right. You're not gonna have space to
reflect. You're not gonna have space to
stop and just wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Right. That's going to be
you. You're not going to have that.
You're just going to do things.
Whether you like it or not,
>> but you
Great.
>> Okay. So, you know, that's
>> that's great, you know. So, but um
that's you and that's dumb, you know.
It's I don't know. I don't I just don't
know, you know. That's I wouldn't spend
my time that way. Like, it's just makes
you look kind of stupid,
right? Like, imagine spending your life
like that.
Imagine that. Imagine every second of
your life you have to like do something
that's like [__] Every second you
you just can't stop it
cuz you want to have your five minutes
of entertainment. Well, there you go.
There you go. The world is still turning
to [__] right? As long as you can
distract yourself from it. As long as
you can give down votes and make sure
that never gets hurt. We don't want that
to get out into the world. God forbid
people know the truth about the world.
Yeah. God forbid that we all know the
truth about what's going on. God forbid
that you sit five minutes down and
listen to the truth that's going on in
the world. No. God forbid, right? You
couldn't have that. So, you better go
download
block out the truth. You can't do that.
It's never going to work. But you're
just What are you doing? What are you
doing? Why? Why would you ruin my life?
Why would you ruin my life? Why would
you spend any amount of time ruining my
life? Why would you do that? I'm doing
good things in this world. I do nothing
bad. Not a single thing. I only do good
things.
What's wrong with you if you don't if
you are the person that's going to stand
in the way of a person doing good things
and telling the truth? Why are you the
person that's standing in the way of
truth,
life,
life affirmation, good things, good
messages,
something that could help the world? Why
are you so busy blocking that out and
making sure that nobody hears that? Why
are Why are you Why are you the person
that's death affirming, rotten to the
core, full of [__] doing the exact
opposite than what I teach? Why are you
even here? Why? Why?
Why are you here if you don't want to be
here?
Th ask yourself that. Don't Don't
[__] like for once in your life stop
and think about the things I'm saying.
Why are you here if you don't like me?
Why are you here if you want to ruin
things? Stop this behavior. You're what
40 years old? Like I don't care, dude.
And you do this. Like stop. This is like
you do too many of these things, okay?
And you don't think about it. You don't
think about it. You just do things. But
you never stop to think. And if you do,
like what the conclusion have you come
to that you should waste your entire
life away going to a person to download
their channel because that suits you
because that's like oh that's the
essence of life. If is that where you
derive to your like oh that's the
meaning of life is to go to a random
person channel download their life
because I I certainly don't want that to
get out to anywhere else. What's what's
in your brain if that's your motives
operandom? Huh?
What's in your I just woke up, dude. Got
on on stream. Showed a video and you're
already hating it.
You're already obsessed
with getting my attention, putting me
down. And dude, like that's such a waste
of your life. Every day is a blessing
given to you by the grace of God. And
you desecrate that
that thing that you get, right? You can
breathe. Your heart beats, right? Every
day you wake up. That's a gift from God.
That's a gift that God gives you. Gives
it to me. You use that gift to ruin my
life with.
and you're somehow going to make a
statement or make some kind of argument
that you're doing the right thing and
God said no to me right and you're
desecrating that thing that freedom that
God gave you to to live a life and
you're saying no I don't want to live a
life I just want to hate this guy this
one guy I want to give all my negative
attention all my death spiraling death
ideologies I'll project that onto this
one guy and that's going to Give me my
purpose in life. Really, Nick? Really?
Really? Really? That's what gives you
purpose in life? To sit and download me
all day.
That's it. That's what you do in your
life.
What a purpose. What a [__] purpose
you are. I mean, give yourself a round
of applause. You exist only to do that.
Wow.
Did you ever stop and think like what's
in your brain? What are what are you
even thinking? What? So what am I doing
to this world that's so bad according to
you? Right? Because I just come here. I
just tell the truth. I I tell you what's
going on inside Europe. You don't like
it. You're willing to ruin my life. Like
what's wrong with you? What's wrong with
you? Why? I'm looking at you. You don't
answer. You don't You can't say
anything. You can't defend yourself. You
just you're just like you're you're
insufferable.
You are insufferable. Do you sit and
wait for me to get online so you can
hate me? That's even more pathetic. What
a creep.
You're just not You're not just
pathetic. You're a [__] creep, dude.
You sit wait for me to get online so you
can project hatred onto people. That's
the [__] saddest thing I ever heard.
Now extrapolate that six years, right?
Let me see. How many days is that?
You spent
you spent how many?
You spent more than 2,500 days
wasting your life away hating people.
And then you wonder why there's cancer
growing inside of you. You spent every
second of your life desecrating the
thing, the grace that God gave you. Your
life, the fact that you can breathe.
Have you ever said thank you to God for
that? Or do you just wake up every day
and say, "Fuck you, God. I have cancer.
Why? I I Why did you give me that [__]
Like, what the [__] did I I didn't You
deserve it. You deserve it. You [__]
deserve it. If I was God, I would have
given you cancer three times more.
Because every single time God has given
you a second chance, you have wasted it
away. Every single time.
You've been asked many times to stop the
[__] you're doing against me. And I told
you, you get cancer. You're gonna be in
my way. You're gonna get cancer because
God does not like you. I have a purpose
here. You don't. If your purpose is to
harass and annoy me, you have no purpose
in life. But I'm here to help humanity
wake up from the slumber that we in and
create a revolution and bring the
politicians out of out of politics and
create a better world to live in. If
you're against that, then what side are
you on? Who are you who are you with?
Who are you with? Who are you actually
with? If you're if you are against me,
are you working for a lizard? Are you
are you Jewish? Are you like, what's
what's wrong with you? Are you wearing a
small kippa and you want to destroy the
entire world? What's wrong with you?
What is what's actually wrong with you?
Like, open your [__] mouth. Are you
going to talk? No, you're not.
What's wrong with you? So, what's wrong
with you? Yeah. Oh no. Okay. You don't
want to have the conversation. You just
want to be a [__] Okay. Well, you're a
little [__] You're a little [__]
Yeah. You're a little [__] You're a
[__] You are a [__]
Oh, well. Good luck. Good. Good job.
Well, I hope you feel better because um
you know that's all for you and I I can
see the downloads.
I know you it's it's these these people.
You know why you're a slug? Because
everything you do is the opposite of
what you should be doing. You're a
disgrace to God. You're a disgrace to
life. You're a disgrace to all things
good.
You're a disgrace
and I hope God is going to cut you down.
Like just like you you take your own you
take whatever into your own hands.
You're you're a disgrace by God. You're
a disgrace.
You guys are wicked people. But um
no, I'm not going to not going to
address that anymore. You live your life
in darkness, you're going to go to hell.
So, I urge you guys to get away from me
because
I don't I don't I don't want that. Also,
I'm going to remove a lot of people
because I don't want you guys
going to call people and kick them out
of my life today.